Now that you've seen what
a simple convnet looks like,
이제는 간단한 convnet이 어떻게 보이는지 보았으므로,
there are many things that
we can do to improve it.
우리가 개선 할 수있는 많은 것들이 있습니다.
We're going to talk about three of them,
pooling, one by one convolutions and
우리는 세 가지에 대해 이야기 할 것입니다. 풀링,
something a bit more advanced
called the inception architecture.
하나씩의 컨볼 루션 및 초기 아키텍처라는 조금 더 진보 된 것입니다.
The first improvement is a better way
to reduce the spatial extent of your
첫 번째 개선은 컨벌루션 피라미드에서 기능 맵의
feature maps in
the convolutional pyramid.
공간 범위를 줄이는 더 좋은 방법입니다.
Until now, we've used striding to shift
the filters by a few pixel each time and
지금까지 우리는 스트라이드를 사용하여
reduce the future map size.
매 픽셀 몇 픽셀 씩 필터를 조정하고 미래 맵 크기를 줄입니다.
This is a very aggressive
way to downsample an image.
이것은 이미지를 다운 샘플링하는 매우 공격적인 방법입니다.
It removes a lot of information.
그것은 많은 정보를 제거합니다.
What if instead of skipping
one in every two convolutions,
두 번의 회선에서 하나를 건너 뛰는 대신에, 우리는 여전히 아주 작은 보폭,
we still ran with a very small stride,
say for example one.
예를 들면 하나를 가지고 달렸습니다.
But then took all the convolutions in a
neighborhood and combined them somehow.
그런 다음 이웃에있는 모든 회선을 가져 와서 어떻게 든 결합했습니다.
That operation is called pooling, and
there are a few ways to go about it.
그 작업을 풀링 (pooling)이라고하며, 여기에 대해서는 몇 가지 방법이 있습니다.
The most common is max pooling.
가장 일반적인 것은 최대 풀링입니다.
At every point in the future map,
look at a small neighborhood around that
미래지도의 모든 지점에서 그 지점 주변의 작은 이웃을보고
point and compute the maximum
of all the responses around it.
그 지점의 모든 응답의 최대 값을 계산하십시오.
There are some advantages
to using max pooling.
최대 풀링을 사용하면 몇 가지 장점이 있습니다.
First, it doesn't add to
your number of parameters.
첫째, 매개 변수의 수가 증가하지 않습니다.
So you don't risk
an increasing over fitting.
따라서 지나치게 피팅하는 위험은 없습니다.
Second, it simply often
yields more accurate models.
둘째,보다 정확한 모델을 산출하는 경우가 많습니다.
However, since the convolutions that
run below run at a lower stride,
그러나, 그 convolutions 때문에 아래보다 낮은 보폭에서 실행하면
the model then becomes a lot
more expensive to compute.
모델은 계산하기가 훨씬 더 비쌉니다.
And now you have even more hyper
parameters to worry about.
이제는 더 많은 하이퍼 매개 변수가 걱정됩니다.
The pooling region size, and
the pooling stride, and no,
풀링 영역 크기와 풀링 스트라이드는
they don't have to be the same.
동일 할 필요는 없습니다.
A very typical architecture for
규약된 전형적인 아키텍처는
a covenant is a few layers
alternating convolutions and
컨볼루션과 최대 풀링을 번갈아 가며 몇 개의 레이어를
max pooling, followed by a few
fully connected layers at the top.
연결 한 다음 맨 위에 몇 개의 완전히 연결된 레이어를 연결 한 것입니다.
The first famous model to use this
architecture was LENET-5 designed by
이 아키텍처를 사용하는 최초의 유명한 모델은 1998년
Yann Lecun to the character
recognition back in 1998.
Yann Lecun이 문자 인식으로 설계 한 LENET-5입니다.
Modern convolutional networks
such as ALEXNET, which
famously won the competitive ImageNet
object recognition challenge in 2012,
used a very similar architecture
with a few wrinkles.
Another notable form of
pooling is average pooling.
Instead of taking the max,
just take an average over the window
of pixels around a specific location.
It's a little bit like providing
a blurred low resolution view of
the feature map below.
We're going to take
advantage of that shortly.